Kaely Michels-Gualtieri SWINGING TRAPEZE ARTIST



PERSONAL PROFILE

World-renowned swinging trapeze artist with over a decade of professional experience. Trained by both Alexander Doubrovski and Victor Fomine. Skill set also includes flying trapeze, static trapeze, hoop, silks and acrobatics. Strong public speaker, proficient in several languages, nationally registered Emergency Medical Technician, strong scientific background, including lab work, and extensive media experience.

PROFESSIONAL CIRCUS EXPERIENCE

Big Apple Circus | USA Tour | Feb - June 2019 Circo Atayde | Mexico City, Mexico | Feb - June 2019 Festival du Cirque de Massy | Paris, France | Jan 2019 Winter Circus Apeldorn | European Tour | Nov - Dec 2018 Festival du Cirque de Namur | Namur, France | Oct 2018 Festival Sucede | Guadalajara, Mexico | Oct 2018 Le Grande Cirque | Manila, Philippines | Dec 2016 Circus Kobzov | Odessa, Ukraine | July - Aug 2015 Golden Trick Festival | Odessa, Ukraine | July 2015 Circo Hermanos Vazques | USA Tour | April - July 2015

Circus Vargas | USA Tour | Feb - March 2015 Festival du Cirque Rhône Alpes Voiron, France | Dec 2015 Ringling Brothers | USA Tour | Nov 2014- Nov 2015 Star Parivaar Awards | Mumbai, India | June 2014 NoFit State Circus | Blackpool, England | Jan - Feb 2014 Corpus Acrobatics | Luxembourg, Luxembourg | Dec 2013 Circus Gerbola | Ireland Tour | Sep - Nov 2013 Cirque Italia | USA Tour | June - Aug 2013 L'Invention du Monde MC93 | Paris, France | May 2010 Cirque de Demain (Acrobatic Troupe) | Paris, France | Jan 2010

EDUCATION

Brown Univeristy | Sep 2016 - June 2018

Working towards a BS in Biochemistry, GPA 3.84/4.00

NEIMS | Nationally Registered Emergency Medical Technician (EMT) | August 2014

L'Academie Fratellini | Diplômes des Métiers d'Art | Sep 2009 - June 2012

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

McGill University | Research Assistant in the Perepichka Lab | Sep 2016 - June 2018

 Research synthesis and characterization of radical organic framework via solid state polymerization Huntsman Cancer Institute | Research Assistant in the Schiffman Lab | May 2018

o Won the Guiliano Fellowship to research how elephant p53 vs. human p53

Brown University | Research Assistant in the Rose-Petruck Lab | April 2016 - 2018

• Research X-Ray scatter imaging to improve commercial battery cells

Brown University | Regenerative Medicine: Stem Cell Research | Sep 2016 - June 2018

MEDIA

Featured in: USAEOP, 2018 | The Providence Journal, 2017 | Brown Daily Herald, 2017 | ABS CBN News, 2017 | Viva Manilela,

2017 | InterAksyo, 2017 | Generations, 2016 | The Advocate, 2015 | The Wichita Eagle, 2015 | Houma Times, 2015 |

Next Times Record, 2015 | Enertainment, 2015 | The Washington Post, 2013 | The Associated Press, 2013 |

The Baltimore Times, 2013 | WTOP, 2013

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Cell Phone | +1-202-669-9780 **Email** | Trapezekaely@gmail.com Webpage | Trapezekaely.com

Age | 29

Height | 5'3 ft, 160 cm

Weight | 120 pounds, 55 kilos

Nationalities | American and British Native Language | English

Proficient in | French, Italian, Spanish

